export const quizQuestions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: 'Why did Vitalik cross the road?',
    answers: [
      'He was bored',
      'A tiger was chasing him',
      'To get to the other side',
      'This question makes no sense in the multi-verse in which Vitalik lives'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To get to the other side'
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: '4 - 2 = __',
    answers: [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: 'Satoshi _______',
    answers: [
      'Koskinen',
      'Abadi',
      'Ganbaatar',
      'Nakamoto'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Nakamoto'
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: 'Why did you cross the road?',
    answers: [
      'He was bored',
      'A tiger was chasing him',
      'To get to the other side of the street',
      'This question makes no sense in the multi-verse in which Vitalik lives'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To get to the other side of the street'
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: '4 - 1 = __',
    answers: [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: 'Vitalik _______',
    answers: [
      'Koskinen',
      'Abadi',
      'Ganbaatar',
      'Buterin'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Buterin'
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: 'Why did the cat cross the road?',
    answers: [
      'He was bored',
      'A tiger was chasing him',
      'this is the correct answer',
      'This question makes no sense in the multi-verse in which Vitalik lives'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'this is the correct answer'
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: '4 - 3 = __',
    answers: [
      0,
      1,
      2,
      3
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: 'one, two,  _______',
    answers: [
      'Koskinen',
      'Abadi',
      'Ganbaatar',
      'three'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'three'
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: 'four, five, _______',
    answers: [
      'Koskinen',
      'Abadi',
      'Ganbaatar',
      'six'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'six'
  }
];



// {
//   number:
//   question:
//   answers: [],
//   correctAnswer:
// }
